[{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980275868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":22542,"timeElapsed":85624},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980292518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":16649,"timeElapsed":102274},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980306962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":14443,"timeElapsed":116718},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980314280,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":7317,"timeElapsed":124036},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980328922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":14641,"timeElapsed":138678},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980362838,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":33915,"timeElapsed":172594},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980380853,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":18014,"timeElapsed":190609},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980388180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":7326,"timeElapsed":197936},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980400475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":12294,"timeElapsed":210231},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980433184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":31005,"timeElapsed":242940},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980437231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":4046,"timeElapsed":246987},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980445759,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":8527,"timeElapsed":255515},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980457312,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":11551,"timeElapsed":267068},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980466569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":9257,"timeElapsed":276325},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980469962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3391,"timeElapsed":279718},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980476040,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":6077,"timeElapsed":285795},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980482828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":6787,"timeElapsed":292583},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980486380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3551,"timeElapsed":296136},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980500324,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":12700,"timeElapsed":310079},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980511578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":11254,"timeElapsed":321334},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980518909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":7330,"timeElapsed":328665},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980528948,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10037,"timeElapsed":338703},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980540484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":11535,"timeElapsed":350239},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980545939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":5455,"timeElapsed":355695},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980560941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":15001,"timeElapsed":370697},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980564261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3319,"timeElapsed":374017},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980566917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2655,"timeElapsed":376673},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980569081,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2163,"timeElapsed":378837},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980593593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":23366,"timeElapsed":403349},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980597265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3671,"timeElapsed":407021},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980605047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":7781,"timeElapsed":414803},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980611753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":6705,"timeElapsed":421509},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980621913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":10159,"timeElapsed":431669},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980625477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3563,"timeElapsed":435233},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980630839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":5361,"timeElapsed":440595},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980633863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3023,"timeElapsed":443619},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980640007,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":6143,"timeElapsed":449763},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980652687,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":11523,"timeElapsed":462443},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980656349,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3661,"timeElapsed":466105},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980660875,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4525,"timeElapsed":470631},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3579,"timeElapsed":474211},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980668535,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":4079,"timeElapsed":478291},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2533,"timeElapsed":480825},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980676421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":5351,"timeElapsed":486177},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980679223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2801,"timeElapsed":488979},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980681745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2521,"timeElapsed":491501},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980711691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":28771,"timeElapsed":521447},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980713673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":1981,"timeElapsed":523429},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980718857,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5183,"timeElapsed":528613},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980722767,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":3909,"timeElapsed":532523},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980725293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2525,"timeElapsed":535049},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980728997,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3703,"timeElapsed":538753},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980730415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1417,"timeElapsed":540171},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980733457,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3041,"timeElapsed":543213},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980735283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1825,"timeElapsed":545039},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980737413,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2130,"timeElapsed":547169},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980750107,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":11509,"timeElapsed":559863},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980754319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4211,"timeElapsed":564075},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980763837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":9517,"timeElapsed":573593},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980766323,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2485,"timeElapsed":576079},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980771825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":5501,"timeElapsed":581581},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980776351,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":4525,"timeElapsed":586107},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980780151,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3799,"timeElapsed":589907},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980784218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4066,"timeElapsed":593974},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980787523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3304,"timeElapsed":597279},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980802451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":13801,"timeElapsed":612207},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980804497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2045,"timeElapsed":614253},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980808609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":4111,"timeElapsed":618365},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980810943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2333,"timeElapsed":620699},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980813629,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2685,"timeElapsed":623385},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980816519,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2889,"timeElapsed":626275},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980822507,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":5987,"timeElapsed":632263},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980825709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3202,"timeElapsed":635465},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980828147,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2437,"timeElapsed":637903},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980840421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":11113,"timeElapsed":650177},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980842645,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2223,"timeElapsed":652401},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980846969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4323,"timeElapsed":656725},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980851155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":4185,"timeElapsed":660911},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980853807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2651,"timeElapsed":663563},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980856431,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2623,"timeElapsed":666187},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980858633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2201,"timeElapsed":668389},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980862381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3747,"timeElapsed":672137},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980864661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2279,"timeElapsed":674417},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980879644,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":13996,"timeElapsed":689400},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980881115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1470,"timeElapsed":690871},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980882785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1669,"timeElapsed":692541},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980884221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1435,"timeElapsed":693977},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980886362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2140,"timeElapsed":696118},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980888119,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1756,"timeElapsed":697875},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980891781,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3662,"timeElapsed":701537},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980894631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2849,"timeElapsed":704387},{"subjectID":"lfngbs0k9l","prolificID":"6761312f87e4c57c3259eb11","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249eb64bf78729eaba5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980896451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1819,"timeElapsed":706207}]